(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T17:11:04.342803",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
言の葉を紡いで
Spinning leaves of words,
微睡んだ泡沫
slumbering bubbles,
旅人迷い込む
travelers wander into
御伽の深い霧
a fairy tale's deep fog.
差し伸べた手のひら
The palm of an outstretched hand,
そっと触れる予感
a premonition of a gentle touch.
受け止めて零れた
Caught and spilling over,
光の一雫
a single droplet of light.
面影移ろって
Faces shifting away,
微笑んだ幻
a smiling illusion.
思いの果てる場所
The place where thoughts end
まだ遥か遠くで
is still far, far away.
求め探しして彷徨ってやがて歌われて
Seeking, searching, wandering, eventually sung,
幾千幾万幾億の旋律となる
becoming melodies of countless billions.
いつか失い奪われて消える定めでも
Even if fated to be lost, stolen, and fade,
それは忘れられることなき物語
it is a tale that will never be forgotten.
指先を絡めて
Intertwining fingertips,
触れる誰かの夢
someone's dream we touch.
言の葉を紡いで
Weaving words together,
微笑んだ歌かた
a fleeting song with a gentle smile.
旅人迷い込む
A traveler wanders astray
御伽の深い霧
into a fairy tale's deep fog.
差し伸べた手のひら
Reaching out an open palm,
そっと触れる予感
a gentle premonition of touch.
受け止めて零れた
Catching what overflowed,
光の一雫
a single droplet of light.
面影移ろって
Reflections shift and fade,
微笑んだ幻
a smiling illusion.
想いの当てる場所
The place where feelings belong
また遥か遠くて
is still so far away.
言の葉を紡いで
Weaving words together,
微笑んだ歌かた
a fleeting song with a gentle smile.
おくそくしなさいご主人様
Make your guesses, Master!
隣に座ってせーの
Sit down beside me, ready, set—
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ教えて笑顔でアッププ
Who's even happy with this? Teach me, with a smiling up-pu!
朝を忘れてご主人様
Forgetting the morning, Master,
あたしを捕まえてせーの
catch me, ready, set—
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ教えて笑顔でアッププ
Who's even happy with this? Teach me, with a smiling up-pu!
左ハラリ女の子
Fluttering to the left, a girl,
ふわりふわり言葉のゾーン
softly, softly in a zone of words.
それでつまり収めなと感情的リアル笑顔でアッププ
In short, keep your emotions contained—real smile, up-pu!
人は見かけによりぬもの
People aren't always what they seem,
嘘は嘘と見抜けない
you can't always tell lies from truth.
出立からそれる裾の川
From the start, straying from the hem's edge—
踊り明かせハラハラワンツードロー
Dance the night away, thrilling one, two, draw!
欲しかった星目をとらぎます
Capturing the star you wanted,
あたし踊れせーの
dance with me, ready, set—
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ遊びましょ笑顔でアッププ
Who's even happy with this? Let's play, with a smiling up-pu!
左ハラリここは何処
Fluttering left, where are we now?
ふわりふわりぞとかれみしよん
Softly, softly, sort of let me show.
それでつまり収めなと局所的リアル笑顔でアッププ
In short, keep it contained—local real smile, up-pu!
歌い出す夢見るの鐘終わることのないこの世界
The bell of dreams begins to ring in this endless world.
悲しい子供は虚しい子供は
Let the sad children, the empty children, fall asleep.
眠らせて
Fall asleep...
おままごと遊びましょ笑顔でアッププ
Let's play house, with a smiling up-pu!
左ハラリ女の子
Fluttering left, a girl,
ふわりふわり言葉のゾーン
softly, softly in a zone of words.
それでつまり収めなと感情的リアル笑顔でアッププ
In short, keep your emotions contained—real smile, up-pu!
遊びましょ笑顔でアッププ
Let's play, with a smiling up-pu!
アッププ
Up-pu!
はーい、オッマイガッ！ ハロー、エブリワン！ It's the ancient weapon from Hololive ID second generation, Anya Melfissa!
Hii, oh my god! Hello, everyone! It's the ancient weapon from Hololive ID 2nd Generation, Anya Melfissa!
サンキュー、ソ―マッチ、フォーカミング、トゥーマイ、スリーディー、バースデー、ライブ！オッマイガッ、ファイナリー、ファイナリー、ファイナリー！はあ！
Thank you so much for coming to my 3D birthday live! Oh my god, finally, finally, finally! Haah!
今日はね、アーニャの誕生日ということで、え、スリーディー…
Today is, well, Anya's birthday, so, uh, 3D...
で、聖誕祭ライブです、やった！
And so, it's my birthday live stream, yay!
ねえ、見に来てくれてありがとうみんな
Hey, thank you everyone for coming to see me!
Oh my god, I'm so excited!
I'm so, so excited, especially since it's my first 3D birthday live, yes!
I am so excited, and I've still got a few more songs to sing to you guys.
But first of all, remember to post a lot with this hashtag #CuriousTune3D!
Remember to post a lot of screenshots and a lot of your favorite moments. このハッシュタグでぜひみんないっぱいポストしてくれた後で見るから！
Remember to post a lot of screenshots and a lot of your favorite moments!
I'll be checking them out after the live! Please, please, yeah.
I think I like the title a lot. I like the title of the 3D birthday live a lot.
I think it's pretty unique. True the Curious Tune. Yeah, I like that title.
Hmm, sounds pretty unique. Sounds very Anya-like.
And it sure fits the stage!
Look at this! Look at the stage, the 3D birthday live stage! Isn't it so cool and cute?
It's very cool and cute, oh my god!
ねえ、このステージめちゃすごくない？
Hey, isn't this stage super amazing?
ここでね、あのいっぱい歌うの。これからいっぱい歌うんだけど、マジで楽しみ！
And here, I'm gonna sing so many songs. I'm gonna sing lots from now on, I'm seriously looking forward to it!
I can't wait to sing a few more songs in this stage after this!
I can't wait to sing a few more songs on this stage after this!
And then, at the end, oh my god, at the end, I'll be singing my new original song! So be sure to watch until the end.
ねえ、今日はね、最後でなんと折り曲く? 新しい折り曲く 聞けるかもしれないのでみんなね、最後まで見てね！
Hey, today, at the very end... we might even get to hear a brand new original song, so everyone, make sure to watch until the end!
ということで、ここからまだまだ行きますよ、まだまだ歌っていきますよ
And with that, we're going to keep going from here, keep on singing!
ゲストさんたちとね、I'll be singing with some guests, some very, very special guests. So I hope you guys are as excited as I am! Yay! Woohoo!
I'll be singing with some guests, some very, very special guests. So I hope you guys are as excited as I am! Yay! Woohoo!
So, shall we go to the next song? Shall we go to the next song? Oh my god, what is it going to be? What's the next song?
次のかくは…なんだろうな？いきますかね？次の曲は。じゃあね、いきましょう！次の曲は The next song is...
What could the next song be? Shall we go? The next song is...
アイパイダンスホール！やった、レッツゴー！
Aipai Dance Hall! Yay, let's go!
アイパイダンスホール 今日はボレロ とろけちゃうショータイム
Aipai Dance Hall, today's a bolero, a melting showtime
お疲れサワー モレモレよ お代わりはアンコールしないね？
Good work, sour, overflowing! Won't you ask for an encore refill?
終わらないラプコードのダンスで
In an endless rap-code dance
割り切れない気持ち抱えてるよ
Holding feelings that can't be divided
ラブ神もゲンスイもエンジンもエンジン組んで仲良くやれるからとか
Love gods, elementals, engines teaming up to get along well
割り切れない命 小さいのヘブン
Lives that can't be divided, small heaven
今夜はいいんじゃない？
Isn't tonight alright?
踊ればいいんじゃない？
Shouldn't we just dance?
呪い呪われ 残生 原生 汚染温泉
Cursing and cursed, remaining life, current life, polluted hot spring
何ってんだ？
What are you saying?
昂った感情の 世界 圧倒的愛情の Wi-Fi
A world of heightened emotions, overwhelming love's Wi-Fi
持ち寄ってちょっと整えライトレステルが重なって
Bringing them together, slightly adjusting, light-less-tel overlapping
限界まで緩い野獣の状態 厚みとパインみたいだね
A state of loose beast to the limit, thick like a pine tree
パイパイダンスホール ほれほれよ とろけちゃうショータイム アマズッパイレモンキューアイシュリバイマンバイダイ
Aipai Dance Hall, look, look, a melting showtime, bittersweet lemon, Q.I. Shuri, bay, bye-bye!
カムパイカムサニ ほれほれよ 見る気満々ね 愛より圧倒的の中 パッパ ラッパ パッパ
Kampai, kamsani, look, look, so eager to watch, within overwhelming love, pa-pa, trumpet, pa-pa!
鳴り止まない脳内 ノリの良ジョンノーも相棒かい？ 話そうズビポのサイトエンダンスホールじゃ暇神もヒーロー
Endless brain rhythm, are you also a partner with good vibes? Talking Zuvipo's site and dance hall makes even the leisure god a hero
コムサイナ 今日はボレロ 待ちわびてジヌイの贅沢だって笑わせ
Comsaina, today's a bolero, making me laugh at the luxury of waiting for jinui
全人類好戦武闘会の目覚まし的1日はエンジン維持してバイナリな要脳みそモータートロトロのようの
Every human being's militant martial arts tournament alarm-like day, keeping the engine going, binary key brain motor melting like toro
実現オフロガニーおナイト踊りまして煩悩をソサイ突きまして手順を総裁 パッパ ラッパ パッパ
Realizing bath-gany on-night dancing, thrusting worldly desires, managing procedures step-by-step, pa-pa, trumpet, pa-pa!
人類最高のダンスタイム
Humanity's ultimate dance time!
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dancehall
今日はボレロ
Today is a bolero
ぼくらが生まれてはじめて知る音は心臓のコードだろ
The first sound we knew when we were born is our heartbeat's chord
とんとんとんとんとんとんてんとんとん
Stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp, beat, stomp, beat
それはリズムと知った
Knowing that was the rhythm
にしえも今時も
From ancient times to modern days
バイビトが僕たちをつないでんだろう
Vibits are connecting all of us, right?
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパイ！パイ？
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pie! Pie?
愛！いっぱい！でほれほれろ
Love! So much! So get all fired up
とろけた少年甘酸っぱいレモン
A melting boy, bittersweet lemon
求愛人類パイ満杯で乾杯！
Love-seeking humanity, cups full of pie, cheers!
完全にほれほれろ
Completely get all fired up
ミルフィーユみたいね愛ほろり
Like mille-feuille, a melting love
頭の中パッパッパッパッパッパッパッ
Inside my head, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
まるでバージンロードで踊ってるみたい生まれ変わったような気分にして
Like dancing down the virgin road, making me feel like I'm reborn
今宵はボレロ
Tonight is a bolero
マジ割って人類馬鹿になって笑って
Seriously break it down, humanity turning foolish and laughing
おかわり欲しいでしょ？
You want seconds, right?
終わりは近づけどさ
Even as the end draws near
終わらないパイのように続けたい
I want it to go on like an endless pie
計算なんてできないが…！
Though I can't calculate it...!
愛包ダンスホール 今日はボレロ
Aipai Dancehall, today is a bolero
とろけた少年 甘酸っぱいレモン
A melting boy, bittersweet lemon
求愛人類は パイ満杯だい乾杯！
Love-seeking humanity, cups full of pie, cheers!
またあした来てね あなたならいつでもいいよ
Come back tomorrow, anytime is fine for you
さよならプリンセス 宙に舞っている
Sayonara Princess, fluttering in the sky
眠り沈むその姿は華やかな魅惑のハッピーエンド
The sleeping, sinking form is a gorgeous, alluring happy end
私とさよならだ
It's goodbye to me
鏡の中 独り縛られて
Bound alone inside the mirror
頭の中 逃げ回る毎日です
Running around in circles inside my head every day
ずっと ずっと
Always, always
だって私 変わりないし
Because I never change
夢もないし 口もないし
No dreams, no words
つまらないし 可愛くもないし
Not interesting, not even cute
分からないし 仕方ないし
Don't understand, can't help it
不意に気づいたらまるで 指輪が首輪になっていたんだ
Suddenly noticing my ring had turned into a collar
壊れた大人の愛情なんだ
It's a broken adult's affection
期待を踏んだ私のことなんて気にしないでね
Don't worry about someone like me who stepped on expectations
さよならプリンセス 宙に舞っている
Sayonara Princess, fluttering in the sky
独り浮かぶその姿は 鮮やかな理想のハッピーエンド
The alone-floating form is a vivid, ideal happy end
私とさよならだ 間抜けたプリンセス 過去とバイバイだ
It's goodbye to me, a foolish princess, bye-bye to the past
この際だから全てを燃やしてしまおう
Since we're at it, let's burn everything away
このまま宙を泳いで あの星になれたら
If I could swim through the cosmos and become that star
私、私とさよならだ
It's goodbye to me, to myself
心の穴 巣ごみ疼いた体の中
An empty hole in my heart, a throbbing body
空回る毎日です ずっと ずっと
Spinning in circles every day, always, always
だってあなた様イージー 変わらないし 足長いし 面白いし 顔も可愛いし さりげないし 仕方ないし
Because you're so easy, never changing, long-legged, funny, cute-faced, nonchalant, can't help it
溢れるオーラは まるでキラキラ輝く安定剤ね
Overflowing aura is like a sparkling stabilizer
メロメロ私は 面目ないね 古い昨日の私のことなんて探さないでね
I'm head over heels, shame on me, don't look for the me of yesterday
さよならプリンセス 愛に酔っている
Sayonara Princess, drunk on love
独り浮かぶその姿は 鮮やかな理想のハッピーエンド
The alone-floating form is a vivid, ideal happy end
私とさよならだ さよならプリンセス 全てバイバイだ
It's goodbye to me, Sayonara Princess, bye-bye to everything
巡り巡る 幸せに絡まるほど
Circling around, tangling in happiness so much
まぬけたハッピーエンド 可愛くなれたかな
A foolish happy end, did I become cute?
私 私 はすでに分かっていたんだ 叶よさようならか
I, I already knew, farewell to my wishes
ちょっとどうもこうも 煮え切らない
Hey, how's it going? Can't make up my mind
どっちつかずたって まとまらない
Ambivalent, can't pull it together
ひとりぼっちの世界に響く モノローグ
A monologue echoing in a lonely world
あれもこれも 出来やしない？
Can't I do this and that too?
回る回る 思考回路
Merry-go-round of thoughts
ぐだっ て うだっ ていくほど 持て余す ハングリー精神
Hungry spirit I have too much of as I slouch and groan
あっちこっち進んで止まって 袋小路迷宮？
Moving back and forth, stopping in a dead-end maze?
行き止まり… でも諦めない！
A dead end... but I won't give up!
翔ろ天（スターダム）！
Soar to stardom!
ならひとりぼっちじゃつまらないでしょ
Then being all alone is no fun, right?
カオスなメンバー集めて あの星を目指せ
Gather a chaotic crew and aim for that star
まるで掴みやしない 届やしない 願い星まで
Reaching out for the unattainable, unreachable wishing star
梯子をかけて いざ、登ろう かドリーマーズ！
Set up a ladder and let's climb up, dreamers!
扉を開けて いざ登ろう 階段を
Open the door and let's climb the stairs,
おそれもしない 夢も見ない
With no fear, not even dreaming,
ひるみもしない 飽きるほどに
Unflinching, until we're sick of it,
無謀な 愉快な 冒険譚さ
A reckless, joyful adventure tale.
止まらないまま エンターショウタイム
Never stopping, enter showtime!
迷って迷って 動かないの？
Lost and hesitating, not moving?
次のセリフが うんちょっと
What's the next line? Um, wait a second—
まいごになった 世界に降りる
Descending into a lost world,
エンドロールの 名残としてやるのさ
Doing it as a remnant of the end credits.
計算尽く配役の フレーム
A frame of carefully calculated casting,
磨いてたまらない
Polishing it incessantly.
あれこれはんで 悩んで
Thinking over this and that, worrying,
遠回り から回り
Taking detours, spinning in circles.
追いつくのは それこそが
Catching up is precisely why
最高のショウタイム
It's the ultimate showtime!
なら ちっちゃな仕掛けにも 気づけないだろ
Then you wouldn't even notice the tiny tricks, right?
エンジン全開 鼓動上昇コースターで
Full throttle on a coaster of rising heartbeats,
また何にも 手加減はしない
Still not holding back at all.
後悔はしない 救いはしない 不完全燃焼
No regrets, no saving you—incomplete combustion!
花火に乗っけてまた 飛ばそうぜ チャレンジャー
Load it onto fireworks and launch it again, challenger!
暗い空も 涙も 吹き飛ばすように
So as to blow away both dark skies and tears,
照らせよ 歌えよ 目を覚ましてね
Shine, sing, and wake up!
顔を上げて ショーマスト・ゴー・オン
Lift your head, the show must go on!
魔法使いは ワンダーニャン
The wizard is Wonder Nyang,
魂の底まで ナルシスト
A narcissist to the depths of their soul.
決まれ決まれ 一等席で
Strike a pose in the front row!
苛々をちょっと 発散のフレーバー
A bit of frustration as a venting flavor,
磨いててたまらない
Polishing it incessantly.
あいまいなままだって 笑っても
Even if it's vague, smiling,
次はだめだよ 止められやしない
Next time won't do, we can't be stopped!
語り尽くせない 思い出話を詰め込んだ風船
A balloon packed with endless nostalgic memories,
金貨をかけてゆこう 旅人たちをのせて
Let's wager gold coins, carrying the travelers.
まだ終わらない 終わりたくない それでもいつかは
It's not over yet, I don't want it to end, but someday...
その日が来るまで
Until that day arrives,
通りに聞かせ 歌い明かせ
Let it be heard on the street, sing until dawn.
スティイ・ザ・ラスト・パレード 儚い物語を演じよう
Stay the Last Parade, let's act out a fleeting story.
忘れやしない 嘆きやしない 別れじゃないから
We won't forget, we won't lament, because this isn't goodbye.
無謀な 愉快な 伝説は
A reckless, joyful legend—
発展途上だ ステップ・バイ・ステップで はちゃめちゃじゃの
Still a work in progress, step by step, how chaotic!
一つずつ巡るのさ ミスター・ショウタイム
Visiting one by one, Mr. Showtime!
歌ったよー！
We sang!
楽しかったねー！
That was so fun!
みんな来てくれたの？ ありがとう！
Did you all come to see us? Thank you!
お誕生日 おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうなんだけどさ、どういうテンションなのこれ？
Thank you and all, but what kind of vibe is this?
祝い何やってさ こういうテンションだっけ？
Wait, is this how celebration vibes work?
そうなんだ。ちなみにどんなんだと思ってたの？
Is that so? By the way, what kind of vibe did you expect?
お祝いテンションなの？ さてはそうなんだ。
A celebratory vibe? I knew it.
アイリスちゃんは何歳になったの？ 今年は…
Iris, how old are you turning? This year...
え、何ちゃいになったの？ 二ちゃいになったの？
Huh, how many years old? Two years old?
そうだよ！ アイリスは何歳なの？ え、アイリスは…
That's right! How old is Iris? Uh, Iris is...
え、アイリス、はったいなの？
Huh, Iris, are you eight?
聞いてないから！ まだ聞いてないから！
We haven't heard that yet! You didn't listen!
聞いてないから。え、何ちゃいなの？
You didn't listen. Huh, how old are you?
アイリスは はったいなの？
Iris, are you eight?
アイリスは何歳なの？
How old are you, Iris?
アイリスもありがとな。ありがとな。
Thanks to Iris too. Thanks a lot.
頑張った、頑張った。もうやめて、もう。
We did our best, we did our best. Stop it already!
私はもう消えます！ アイリス逃がさないよ！
I'm disappearing now! We won't let you escape, Iris!
恥ずかしいからね！ はあー、疲れた。
Because it's embarrassing! Whew, I'm exhausted.
じゃあ、Mr.Showtime 4人で歌ったんですけども、感想とか曲の感想とか…
Well, the four of us sang 'Mr. Showtime', so what are your thoughts or impressions on the song?
もうめっ ちゃ難しかったの！ まぁね。
It was super, super difficult! Well, yeah.
「高いとこ、低いとこ、どこどこ？」
"High places, low places, where, where?"
「うーん、うーん、あー、確かにね」
"Hmm, hmm, ah, true."
「低いとこばっかだよ、私」
"I'm only in low places."
「あ、リスはね」
"Ah, Risu is."
「あ、でもイケボも買ってみたよね？」
"Ah, but you tried buying a cool voice too?"
「うん、でかさも、ろく、とか、だからも、うーん」
"Yeah, the size too, like six, so, hmm..."
「問題さ、イケボ出すことないよって」
"The thing is, you don't need to do a cool voice."
「ね、イケボアイリス珍しいからさ、たまにはいいんじゃないかな」
"Right, IRyS's cool voice is rare, so sometimes is fine."
「まあ、確かにね、こういうイケボアイリス、レアなんだよね」
"Well, true, a cool voice IRyS like this is rare."
「8歳だもね」
"She's 8 years old, after all."
「8歳なのにね、忘れちゃったよ、8歳なんだよ」
"Even though she's 8, I forgot! She's 8 years old."
「もう、もう、もう、もうね、それはそれ、それはそれ、わかる、わかる」
"Geez, geez, well, that's that, I get it."
「だからみんな、あの、受け取ってね、アイリスのかっこよさを」
"So everyone, please accept IRyS's coolness!"
「でん、でん、8歳！」
"Ta-da, 8 years old!"
「8歳！」
"8 years old!"
「絶対この、この後アーカイブ見返して」
"Definitely rewatch the archive after this!"
「うん、いやだ、いやだ」
"No way, no way."
「見たくない、見返して」
"I don't wanna see it. Rewatch it!"
「見たい見たい、見たくない」
"I wanna see it, I don't."
「もう、忘れないでよ、みんな」
"Geez, don't forget it, everyone!"
「見 て よー」
"Watch it~!"
「やだ、あ、でも、あーちゃんね」
"No, but, A-chan's..."
「ライブはちゃんと見てね、この、この部分だけ飛ばして」
"Make sure to watch the live, just skip this part."
「一番大事なね」
"The most important part!"
「めっちゃん、喉渇いてるな」
"Mecha, my throat is dry."
「あら、急に喉渇いてるから、このテンションは、喉渇く」
"My, your throat suddenly getting dry at this tension?"
「そうか、な」
"Is that so?"
「ほら、喉渇いて、あ、あれ」
"Look, your throat is dry, oh."
「なんか、なんか、お茶持ってないかな」
"Wonder if someone has tea."
「なんかきた、なんかきた、なんか出てきたよ」
"Something came, something came out."
「あーちゃん！」
"A-chan!"
「お、たくさん歌って、喉乾いたでしょ」
"Oh, you sang a lot, your throat must be dry."
「そうだよ」
"That's right."
「これ飲んで欲しいの」
"I want you to drink this."
「なんだり、なんだり」
"What is this?"
「そうだよ、これ」
"That's right, this."
「こぼれる、こぼれる」
"It'll spill, it'll spill."
「なんか、そうだな、の、こぼしてほしい」
"You want me to spill it?"
「はい、これはなにかしら」
"Here, what could this be?"
「え、やばいな、これなにかしら」
"Yikes, what on earth is this?"
「ね、湯気立ってるね、熱々じゃん」
"Hey, it's steaming, it's boiling hot."
「あ、ちちち、熱そうだよ」
"Ah, hot, it looks hot."
「うん、と、熱そう、熱い」
"Yeah, looks hot, it's hot."
「うんで、なんで、ね」
"So why, hey."
「まあ、いったん飲むか」
"Well, I'll drink it for now."
「なんで、なんで？」
"Why, why?"
「で、本当に飲むの？」
"Wait, are you really drinking it?"
「本当にするの、すごいきりし」
"You're really doing it?"
「美味しい、美味しい」
"Delicious, delicious."
「うわー！」
"Whoa!"
「あー、めっ ちゃ、めっ ちゃ美味しかったよ、でも」
"Ah, it was super, super delicious, though."
「美味しかった？」
"Was it good?"
「美味しかったけどさ、めっ ちゃ美味しかった」
"It was good, but super delicious."
「よかった」
"Good for you."
「あ、美味しかった」
"Ah, it was delicious."
「なんだろうね、一体」
"I wonder what on earth it was."
「なんか、分からない」
"I have no idea."
「ちょっと待って！」
"Wait a second!"
「あーちゃん、どういうこと？」
"A-chan, what is the meaning of this?"
「でっかくなっちゃった！」
"I've become huge!"
「あんまり動きも変わんないでしょ」
"Your movements don't even change much."
「ちょっと待って！」
"Wait a minute!"
「でかくなっちゃったんだけど、ええ！？」
"I got huge, what!?"
「えー！」
"Ehh!?"
「ねえ、すごい揺れるね、潰れるじゃん」
"Hey, it shakes so much, we'll get crushed."
「みんな、みんな潰れるじゃん」
"Everyone will get crushed!"
「神、やめてよ！」
"Kami, stop it!"
「神、潰れるぞ、神、神」
"Kami, you'll crush us!"
「神！」
"Kami!"
「あ、あー、危ない！あー、熱い！」
"Ah, ah, dangerous! Ah, hot!"
「残りは、流せ！」
"Pour the rest away!"
「残りは流せばいい！」
"You should just pour the rest out!"
「残りは流せばいい、元に戻してくださいよ、じゃないと」
"Return us to normal, otherwise..."
「どうしたらいいの？」
"What should we do?"
「潰しちゃうぞ」
"I'll crush you."
"I'll crush you!"
「ね、やだ！」
"Hey, no way!"
「もし、もしかしたら」
"If, perhaps..."
「お茶かければ元に戻るんじゃないの？」
"Won't pouring tea return us to normal?"
「暴力、暴力」
"Violence, violence!"
「え、それだ、やってみようるな、あにゃ」
"Ah, that's it, let's try it, Anya."
「これ、もう一回かけてみたら、足元」
"Try pouring it on her feet again."
「普通にかけるんですか？」
"Do I just pour it normally?"
「ジャブジャブ」
"Splash, splash."
「戻れるか？」
"Can we go back?"
「お、お？」
"Oh, oh?"
「さっきは」
"Earlier..."
「よくもやってくれたな」
"You really did it to us."
「ルーナ先輩、ルーナ先輩、どういう飲み物なんですか、それ！」
"Luna-senpai, what kind of drink is that?!"
「でっかくなったならね」
"Well, if you became huge..."
「そんなことはどうだっていいんだよ」
"That doesn't matter right now!"
「なになに、なになに、なになに」
"What, what?"
「さっきはよくもすっかってやってくれたね」
"You really did that to us earlier."
「ね、あにゃ、あにゃちっちゃくてかわいいね」
"Hey, Anya, Anya is so small and cute."
「え、そうそうそう、そうから、だからね」
"Yeah, yeah, so, therefore..."
「ひどいことしないで」
"Don't do awful things."
「かわいいから、ご褒美にあげちゃ」
"Since you're cute, I'll give you a reward."
「え、どういうご褒美？」
"Eh, what kind of reward?"
「あにゃちゃん」
"Anya-chan."
「おい、それわ」
"Hey, that is..."
「それは、アイリスの足だ、パンチラと見せかけて」
"That's IRyS's leg, pretending to be a panty shot."
「何て、何て残酷な」
"How cruel!"
「痛い、痛い、ちょっと、いじめやりることじゃないよ」
"Ouch, ouch, hey, this isn't bullying."
「ちょっと、にちゃりやることじゃないよ」
"Hey, that's gross."
「いじめだと思いまーす？」
"Do you think this is bullying?"
「でっかいだよ、こんなにちっちゃってかわいいからしかたないね」
"She's huge, but since she's so small and cute, it can't be helped."
「うん」
"Yeah."
「あにゃにさ、プレゼントもあげたことだし、そろそろ帰ろっか」
"Since we gave Anya a present, let's head back soon."
「え？」
"Eh?"
「時間だし、じゃね」
"It's time, see ya."
「元に戻してくださいよ」
"Please return us to normal!"
「その前に」
"Before that..."
「その前に元に戻してくださいよ、ちょ、ちょっと待って！」
"Before that, return us to normal, wait a second!"
「ちょっと待ってーー！」
"Wait a minute!!"
「響かせていく」
"Let it resonate"
「The party's over」
"The party's over,"
「お芝居はおしまい」
"the curtain's falling."
「止まらない We get it, we get it go」
"We won't stop, we get it, we get it go"
「導いて頂戴」
"Lead the way."
「Don't cry あたらしい今も Throwback」
"Don't cry, even into this new now, throwback"
「気後れないように創るから」
"I'll create so I won't hesitate"
「必ず追い付けて見せるから」
"I'll make sure to catch up and show you"
「兎角今迄 正しいことは与えられてた」
"Up until now, we were always given what's right"
「ぼくに足をくれたのは 君だけ」
"You were the only one who gave me legs"
「愛していたい 謳にしないと始まらない」
"I want to love, if I don't sing out, it won't begin"
「歪なステップでもいい? 今は君と踊っていたい」
"Even an awkward step is fine? Now I want to dance with you"
「ただ 生きてための呪いを そこに残した」
"Leaving behind the curse just to live right there"
「命を追ってほしい 君と短く永い季節をたどって」
"Chasing life, tracing short and endless seasons with you"
「いない いない ばぁで はじめまして」
"Peek-a-boo, nice to meet you"
「アナタのVeil どうしても引き剥がして」
"Tearing away your veil no matter what"
「その深い(深い) 瞳に別の色をのせたい」
"I want to put a different hue in those deep eyes"
「老いた 知った 空振りも 今 蹴飛ばして 駆け付けられるから」
"Kicking away past stumbles, I can rush right over now"
「あまねく導いてみせるから」
"I'll guide you everywhere"
「倍々しても 元が何でもない 私に成せることはないが」
"Even doubled, a nobody like me can do nothing, but"
「そうだ きっと今はそれでも良いって」
"Right, I'm sure even now is fine"
「青が湧き拡がる空から」
"From the sky where blue wells up and spreads"
「愛していたい 謳にしないと始まらない」
"I want to love, if I don't sing out, it won't begin"
響かせて
Let it resonate,
The party’s over お芝居はおしまい
The party's over, the show's done.
止まらない
We won't stop,
We get it, we get it go
導いて頂戴
Lead the way,
Don’t cry あたらしい今も
Don't cry, even in this new present.
Throwback
気後れしないように創るから
I'll create it so I won't look back.
必ず追い付いて見せるから
I'll make sure to catch up with you.
浅瀬今際
At the shallow brink,
正しいことは与えられていた僕に
Rightness was given to me,
足をくれたのは
And the one who gave me legs
君だけ
Was only you.
愛していたい 禍にしないと始まらない
I want to love, it won't start without a curse.
歪なステップでもいい? 今は君と踊っていたい
Is a twisted step okay? Right now I want to dance with you.
ただ生きるための呪いをそこに残した 命を追ってほしい
Leaving behind a curse just to live, I want you to chase after life.
君と短く永い季節をたどって
Tracing a short and eternal season with you.
ないないばうで はじめまして アナタの Veil どうしても引き剥がして
Peek-a-boo, nice to meet you. No matter what, tearing away your veil.
その深い 瞳に別の色をのせたい 老いた 知った 空振りも
And putting a different color into those deep eyes. Growing old, knowing, missing the mark...
今 跳ね飛びして駆け付けられるから
Now I can leap and dash forward.
あまねく導いてみせるから
I'll guide you universally.
倍々しても
Even if multiplied,
元が何でもない私に成せることがあるか?
Can I achieve anything when I started as nothing?
でもそうご 結局今はそれでも良いって
Even so, right now I think that's fine.
青が膨らみ拡がる空から
From the sky where blue spreads out,
愛していたい 禍にしないと始まらない
I want to love, it won't start without a curse.
歪なステップでもいい? 今は君と踊っていたい
Is a twisted step okay? Right now I want to dance with you.
ただ生きるための呪いをそこに残した 命を追ってほしい
Leaving behind a curse just to live, I want you to chase after life.
君と短く永い季節をたどって
Tracing a short and eternal season with you.
倍々しても 元が何でもない私に出来ることはあるか?
Even if multiplied, can I achieve anything when I started as nothing?
この Tempo そうご こんな禍ならどうだ
With this tempo, what if this is a curse?
正しくないけれど丁度良いかもね
It might not be correct, but the timing is just right.
もっと響かせて この未知に賭けて
Let it resonate more, betting on this unknown.
充電器を貸して！ またあなたのせいで あたし擦り減った
Lend me your charger! Once again, because of you, I've worn myself out.
終電見逃して またあたしのせいで 帰れなくなった
Missing the last train, and once again, because of me, I couldn't go home.
繋がっていようね、消耗戦に持ち込んで
Let's stay connected, dragging each other into a war of attrition.
お互いに足を引っ張ったアオハル
Our youth, where we both held each other back.
沈殿した思い出でずーっといっしょ！
With sunken memories, together forever!
参観日にだって 誰からも見られていない気がしたんだ
Even on classroom observation day, it felt like no one was looking at me.
散々シニカルって 昼の街に期待しないようにしたんだ
I acted so cynical, trying not to expect anything from the daytime streets.
そうやって守った孤独さえめちゃくちゃになった
Even the solitude I protected that way got completely messed up.
あたしいつでも死にたくて仕方ない
I always want to die so badly.
こんな顔大事にしたいと思えないもん
I can't even think of wanting to cherish a face like this.
共に過ごした日々と ささやかな幸せが
The days we spent together, and that modest happiness,
かけがえのないトラウマになってたらいいな
I hope it turned into an irreplaceable trauma.
離れなければなんて 誰かが吐かせたバグだよね？
Being separated and such, that's just a bug someone forced upon us, right?
あなたの一生の後悔として伴侶遂げるよ
I'll stay by your side as your lifelong regret.
Q.大事なものって、なあに？ A.今喪失したそれ
Q. What's the most important thing to you? A. What you just lost.
あたしと間違いを犯しちゃったんだ
You made a mistake with me.
取り返しがつかないね 健やかなときも病めるときも
There's no turning back now. In sickness and in health,
グロい履歴の中でずーっといっしょ！
Through all our grotesque history, we'll always be together!
もうちょっとふつうに悲しいこと悲しいと思いたかった
I wanted to feel a bit more normally that sad things were sad.
長調のチューンに感情委託して楽になりたかった
I wanted to entrust my emotions to a major-key tune and find some relief.
「せいぜい一生懸命生きてくださいね」
"Do your absolute best to live your life," you say.
あたしいつでも死にたくて仕方ない
I always want to die so badly.
あんな歌の言いなりになりたくないの
I don't want to be made to obey a song like that.
あなただけひとりで あたしの目を盗んで
All by yourself, behind my back,
幸せになろうなんて思わないで
Don't you dare try to go and be happy.
髪を乾かしてくれた夜から あたしは壊されたんだよ
Ever since that night you dried my hair, I've been broken inside.
あなたの一生の後悔として伴侶遂げるよ
I'll stay by your side as your lifelong regret.
外れなくなってしまった指輪みたいに
Like a ring that has become impossible to take off,
何度もずーっとフラッシュバックしてしる、最低だよ
It keeps flashing back over and over, it's the absolute worst.
一緒に居た時の方があたし可愛かったな
I was so much cuter when we were together.
あなたの一生の後悔として伴侶遂げるよ
I'll stay by your side as your lifelong regret.
Q.大事なものって、なあに？ A.今喪失したそれ
Q. What's the most important thing to you? A. What you just lost.
あたしと間違いを犯しちゃったんだ 取り返しがつかないね
You made a mistake with me, there's no turning back now.
健やかなときも病めるときも 他の誰かと眠っていても
In sickness and in health, even if you go to sleep with someone else,
お揃いの悪夢でずーっといっしょ！
Together in matching nightmares, forever together!
排気物に酔ったケイデンス
Cadence drunk on exhaust fumes,
もう嫌なこと全部投げ出して
throwing away everything you hate.
逞しさにどうか聖烈を
Please bestow sanctity on our resilience,
もう新たな話は雲の上の用
and any new story is far above the clouds.
つまんないよ
How boring.
ダークマターのせいで
Because of dark matter,
生まれた時代が悪かったせいで
because of the wrong era I was born into,
全部あなたのせいで
all because of you,
今日傘を持って来るのを忘れた
I forgot to bring an umbrella today.
興味無いそんなトピック
Topics like that don't interest me.
間違いた救済に罪を
"Sin to wrongful salvations,"
抗った群衆に害を
"give harm to rebelling crowds."
ヘルメット頭蓋を割ったようなサウンド
The sound of a skull cracked through a helmet,
ガソリン匂った日常の 黎明の兆候まだ見えない
the dawn of ordinary days smelling of gas is not yet in sight.
叛旗を持ったメーデー
May Day with a banner of rebellion,
もう嫌なこと全部投げ出したいね
I want to abandon everything I hate already.
アイス奢ってくれ
Buy me some ice cream,
今日財布を持ってくるのを忘れた
I forgot to bring my wallet today.
賭けのないポーカーみたいな
Like poker without any bets,
つまらなくなった戦争
this war has grown so boring.
結局他人が怖いのか
In the end, are we just afraid of others?
液晶に映った量子論が
The quantum theory reflected on a screen—
どんな未来を選者に選んで 誰が生贄になるかな
what future will it choose for the winner, and who will be the sacrifice?
誇る鳥は衰え 頭垂れて乞い
An arrogant bird falls, lowering its head to beg.
介錯も無くただ永劫の呵責と寄り添う中やっと見たれ
Without mercy, nestled with eternal remorse, it finally sees—
街は焼けた海 穿たれた福音
cities turned into a scorched sea, a pierced gospel.
汚れた地上の災禍など気に留めず明日は星は輝く爛々
Unfazed by disasters on the foul earth, tomorrow the stars will shine brightly.
ドクター・キドリです 愛・爆破っ テロ
I'm Dr. Kidori, love and explosion, terror!
簡単になれば 埋まったマスター マスター
If it gets simple, the buried master, master—
ドクター・キドリです 愛想良いかも
I'm Dr. Kidori, maybe quite friendly.
朧朧オートも 埋めたメタ メタ
Hazy auto-mode too has buried the meta, meta.
何処にも無いから寝ていたら 壊れて泣いてるユメを診たんだよ
When I was sleeping because there was nowhere to go, I diagnosed a broken, crying dream.
時期には
In due time,
嘘に診えてクルゥ
it starts to look like a lie.
顔が→兇器になっちゃうヨ
Your face → is gonna turn into a weapon!
偽が→権利を取ったんだ
This fake → has seized the rights!
無くなってほしい煩悩が どうやら生き延びてしまった 生き延びてしまったんだ！！
The earthly desires I wanted gone somehow managed to survive!
足が→タガメになっちゃうヨ
Your foot → is gonna become a giant water bug!
嘘が→動機になったんだ
The lie → became the motivation!
疑ってほしい本能を どうやら本心だと思った 本心だと思ったんだ！！
The instinct I wanted you to doubt, I somehow thought was my true feeling!
クチョウ
Kuchou!
皆の苦手な物を教えて欲しい アガルトー
Please tell me everyone's weaknesses, Agartou!
ドクター・キドリです 全部辞めろよ
I'm Dr. Kidori, stop it all already!
アティチュードが 感情物に届く猛毒
Attitude is a deadly poison reaching emotional objects.
損得の得の方だけ 回った割った割った
Only the profit side of win-loss spun and split, split, split!
顔が→兇器になっちゃうヨ
Your face → is gonna turn into a weapon!
偽が→権利を取ったんだ
This fake → has seized the rights!
無くなってほしい煩悩が どうやら生き延びてしまった 生き延びてしまったんだ！！
The earthly desires I wanted gone somehow managed to survive!
音が一機能になってしまう
Sound ends up becoming a single function.
人が→偽りに入集まる
People → gather under false pretenses!
塞がってしまえない耳 どうやら届いていないみたい 届いていないみたいンボ
Ears that can't be plugged up, it seems they aren't reaching anyone at all.
クチョウ
Kuchou!
toruite ne mitai
It's like walking...
toruite ne mitai neku-chan
Like walking around, Neku-chan.
Oh my god!
That was so much fun!
I sang so many songs!
Ya, ippai utatchatta, nē? Gesuto no minasan-tachi tomo ne, utatchaimashita keredomo...
Yeah, I sang a lot, right? I sang together with all the guests too, but...
minna okiniiri toka aru? Dō datta?
did you guys have any favorites? How was it?
How was it? How was all the... How were all the performances?
How was it? How were all the performances?
If you guys have any favorite, don't forget to post with the hashtag, by the way, #CuriousTune3D.
If you guys have any favorites, don't forget to post with the hashtag—by the way, #CuriousTune3D!
Tell me your favorite or like, you know, memorable moments from the 3D birthday live, yippee!
Tell me your favorite or, you know, memorable moments from the 3D birthday live, yippee!
Oh my goodness!
Now, it's announcement time!
Ada ads ya guys, no skipping ads ya guys, by the way.
There are ads, guys. No skipping ads, guys, by the way.
Habis ini akan ada ads, jadi no skipping skipping ya, oke? Don't skip the ads, oke?
There's gonna be an ad after this, so no skipping, okay? Don't skip the ads, okay?
Oh my god! The first one is... the-the-the-the-the-the-the-the-then!
Oh my god! The first one is... the-the-the-then!
Oh my god!
Tanjōbi kinen! 2025-nen noグッズdatte!
Birthday celebration! 2025 merchandise!
The first one is... this beautiful, you know, this beautiful birthday merchandise!
Yes, that's right! We will be having 2025 merchandises, Anya Melfissa merchandises, yippee!
Yes, that's right! We will be having 2025 merchandise, Anya Melfissa merchandise, yippee!
Ada birthday 2025 merchandise, guys, yippee!
There's birthday 2025 merchandise, guys, yippee!
Ini art-nya, art-nya gila keren banget gak sih, guys? Oh my god!
This art, isn't the art insanely cool, guys? Oh my god!
Nah, ilustrasi tu, めっちゃすごくない？
And this illustration, isn't it super amazing?
Nee, kochira no suteki naグッズno key bijuaru wa ne, Sorani-sensei ga tantō shite kudasaimashita! Sugoku suteki na irasuto de watashi mo oki ni iri desu.
Hey, the key visual for this wonderful merchandise was handled by Sorani-sensei! It's such a lovely illustration, it's my favorite too.
Aku suka banget sama illustration, kali ini gila keren banget, Anya banget gak sih?
I love this illustration so much, it's insanely cool this time, is it very Anya-like?
Tekoto de ne, let's do... let-let-let's take a look at each item one by one, shall we?
So, let's take a look at each item one by one, shall we?
Let's look at them. The first one is this!
Rubber Mat! Rubber Mat with the key visual.
Rubber mat pakai key visual yang tadi ya, guys. Yes, keren banget oh my god. Keren banget oh my god! Nah, key visual ga printa serta rubber mat-desu.
Rubber mat using the key visual from earlier, guys. Yes, it's so cool, oh my god. So cool, oh my god! Well, the key visual is printed onto a rubber mat.
Ini bisa dipakai buat meja-meja gak apa-apa, buat main apa ya, buat main board game gitu juga gak apa-apa, terus buat main catur juga gak apa-apa, dibuat tidur juga gak apa-apa, guys. Ya, terserah ya, guys, dibuat tidur juga gak apa-apa, ne?
You can use this for tables, it's fine, for playing board games or whatever is fine too, playing chess is fine too, sleeping on it is fine too, guys. Yeah, whatever you want, guys, sleeping on it is fine too, right?
Ya, you can use this rubber mat anywhere you like, basically.
Yeah, you can use this rubber mat anywhere you like, basically.
And then, the next one...
The next merchandise, Acrylic Diorama Stand! Acrylic diorama standodesu.
The next merchandise, Acrylic Diorama Stand! It's an acrylic diorama stand.
This isn't your usual acrylic stand, by the way.
It's made with three layers for a more dynamic, three-dimensional look, guys! Oh my goodness!
Ini bukan acrylic stand biasa, guys. Ada tiga lapis yang bikin tampilannya kelihatan lebih hidup. Kayak kayak aku kan krisis hidup ya, guys. Cocok banget gak sih?
This isn't your ordinary acrylic stand, guys. There are three layers that make the display look more alive. Like me, who's having a life crisis, you know, guys. Doesn't it fit so well?
The illustration comes with a design frame, so it's perfect for display.
Ne, irasuto ni dezain fureimu ga tsuita disupurei ni pittari no shohin desu. Cocok banget buat display pokoknya, guys.
Hey, it's a product perfect for display with a design frame attached to the illustration. It's totally suited for display, guys.
You can place it on your desk next to the rubber mat as well. Terus di meja kalian tuh rubber mat yang tadi juga bisa.
You can place it on your desk next to the rubber mat as well. And on your desk, the rubber mat from earlier works too.
Terus ya, dibuat, dimakan juga bisa. Dimakan juga sebenarnya bisa, duh. Aduhnya. Biasalah ya, guys, adrenalin dari habis live, jadi ngomongnya aneh-aneh.
And yeah, making it, eating it is also possible. Eating it is actually possible, sigh. Oh dear. Well, you know, guys, the adrenaline from just finishing a live makes me talk weirdly.
Okay, the next merchandise, shall we take a look at the next merchandise?
So cute! Look at this! It's an acrylic keychain of gen- general outfit Anya.
So cute! Look at this! It's an acrylic keychain of general outfit Anya.
Yay! Itsuka-ichou no akuriru kiihorudā desu. Metchaw kawaii kunai?
Yay! It's an acrylic keychain of Anya in her 1st-anniversary general outfit. Isn't it super cute?
Yeah, me in my regular outfit. So cute, mini Anya.
You can take it anywhere, guys! Oh my god! On your back? Hmm. Di tas, juga bisa, terus diapa lagi ya? Di dompet...
You can take it anywhere, guys! Oh my god! On your bag, on your bag too, and what else? On your wallet...
juga bisa, di room pad juga bisa. Terserah deh di mana aja, guys.
You can use it in your room, anywhere you like, guys.
Hmm.
Mhm.
Nih, odekake toka ni ぜひ使ってください。
Please use it when you go out!
Tuh,
So,
次は… こちらです！
next up is... this!
こちらです！
Here it is!
かわいい、kawaikunai?
Cute, isn't it cute?
Kawaii to kakkoii ga, eh, mazariatteru... hand mirror desu!
It's a hand mirror where cuteness and coolness are mixed together!
Designed mirror has a chic design, perfect for using at home or taking it with you when you're out.
It's both stylish and really easy to use.
Nih, kacanya, gila, stylish banget, guys! Terus ada kayak motif-motif aneh gitu di belakangnya, kayak gini nih, guys. Keren banget enggak sih, oh my god!
The mirror is crazy stylish, guys! And there are these weird motifs on the back, like this, guys. Isn't it super cool, oh my god!
Ini perfect banget kalau kalian mau keluar, terus ya, biasanya untuk yang butuh kaca lah, guys. Daripada pakai HP, mending pakai hand mirror-nya Anya Melfissa. Ya enggak sih?
This is perfect if you're going out, and well, usually for those who need a mirror, guys. Instead of using your phone, you might as well use Anya Melfissa's hand mirror. Right?
Chic na design no hand mirror na no de, ie de tsukatte mo yoi shi, osoto de tsukatte mo yoi no tsukaiyasui mirror to natte imasu.
It's a chic-designed hand mirror, so it's easy to use both at home and outside.
Di room aja boleh, guys. Di room, di luar, terserah kalian, okay?
In your room is fine, guys. In your room, outside, however you like, okay?
Next up! Next up is this!
Voice pack! Oh my god, yes! Voice pack, and this time the script is written by yours truly, Anya Melfissa, just like pretty much every year.
Every year I, I write my own birthday voice pack.
Ne, kochira ne, daihon, mata kotoshi mo mata... Anya Melfissa desu. Daihon tantou Anya Melfissa desu. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu. Mainen shinagara no... hai.
And this year's script is also... by me, Anya Melfissa. I'm in charge of the script, Anya Melfissa. Please look forward to it. Doing it every year... yes.
And of course, there are also special bonuses!
You get for buying the merch set! Here are the bonuses.
Postcard with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph.
Yeah, duplicated autograph means, um, the autograph is, you know, a foil stamp.
Nah, menandani jadi kayak dicetak pakai foil stamping ya, guys.
So, the signature is printed using foil stamping, guys.
And don't worry, it's not a limited edition this time, so everyone can get one!
Bukan limited edition, guys. Jadi, oh my god, Beli si, udah enggak limited. Masa enggak beli? Ya enggak? Udah dibuat enggak limited, masa enggak beli, guys? Gila, keterlaluan banget sih.
It's not a limited edition, guys. So, oh my god, just buy it, it's unlimited. How could you not buy it? Right? It's made unlimited, how can you not buy it, guys? Seriously, that's too much.
And then the next bonus! The next bonus is...
The voice pack! The voice pack translations!
Yes, um, I forgot to mention, my voice pack is only available in, you know, in Japanese. So if you guys, you know, gather the bonus, one of them is actually English and Bahasa Indonesia script of my voice pack.
Jadi, um, voice pack-nya cuma ada bahasa Jepang. Tapi tenang aja, guys, bonusnya ada translation bahasa Indonesia sama translation bahasa Inggris juga.
So, um, the voice pack is only in Japanese. But don't worry, guys, the bonus includes Indonesian and English translations as well.
Jadi, tunggu apa lagi? Tunggu apa lagi?
So, what are you waiting for? What are you waiting for?
Nih, kalau cerita, kan, anu, voice-nya, kan, main-nya, bahasa Jepang, kan? Gitu. Tapi, di sini, bonus-nya, bahasa Inggris dan bahasa Indonesia, juga. Jadi, ya, silakan, nikmatin, ya, dengan berbagai bahasa, ya.
Even though the voice acting is in Japanese, you get bonuses in English and Indonesian as well. So please enjoy it in various languages!
To iu koto de, tsugi... kochira desu!
With that said, next... is this!
Yay, special bonus! If you buy the merchandise set, you'll get a special card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game released last September!
Oh my god! What? Friends, ya, yang beli set complete merchandise kali ini, kalian bakal dapat satu kartu yang bisa dipakai di hololive Official Card Game yang rilis September tahun lalu, guys!
Nah, kankai, ne, goods set o go-kounitadaita kata ni, ano, sakunen 9-gatsu ni hatsubai sareta hololive Official Card Game de shiyou dekiru kado ga 1-mai tokuten toshite tsukimasu!
And this time, those who purchase the goods set will receive a card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game released last September as a special bonus!
Ya, kono tokuten ne, meccha yokunai? Ne? Minna TCG suki nanda yo ne? Iya, tanoshi sou da naってずっとおもってるのね、アーニャも。
Yeah, isn't this bonus super great? Right? Everyone loves TCGs, right? Yeah, Anya has always thought it looks fun.
Itsuka watashi mo yaritai na to omoimasu.
I hope I can play it sometime too.
カードいんね、これ推しホロメンカード gitu guys.
For cards, this is an oshi holomem card, gitu guys.
For details about the card and how to play it, please check the website.
ね、カードの所在や遊び方についてはね、ホームページで確認してくださいね。
For details on the card location and how to play, please check the website.
Also, the card will be available in Japanese only, by the way.
日本語、日本語のみですね、カードの方は。
Japanese, Japanese only, for the cards.
This bonus, by the way, is only valid for purchases made at hololive production official shop.
This bonus, by the way, is only valid for purchases made at the hololive production official shop.
Jadi, um, ini bonusnya tuh cuma untuk kalian yang beli di hololive production official shop ya guys.
So, um, this bonus is only for those who buy at the hololive production official shop, guys.
And there's a second announcement as well. We still have announcements? Oh my goodness.
ね、こちらは、あの、次の告知、次のお知らせなんですけれども、なんと、オリジナル曲のMVが出まーす！
Now, as for the next notice, the next announcement... guess what? The MV for my original song is coming out!
オリジナル曲のMVがね、なんと、え、今日この後22時でね、あの、プレミア公開なので楽しみにしていてください。
The MV for my original song is having a premiere release tonight at 10 PM, so please look forward to it.
M3 ori song, M3 guys, habis ini jam 8 ya guys. Jam 8 malam waktu Indonesia Barat habis ini.
M3 ori song, M3 guys, after this at 8 PM, guys. 8 PM WIB, right after this.
The MV of my original song will be released at 10 PM JST after this, after this live.
It will also be released on various music distribution services from, you know, from 12 AM your timezone.
It will also be released on various music streaming services starting at 12 AM in your timezone.
So please look forward to it! 楽曲音楽配信サービスにもね、リリースされるのでお楽しみにしていてください。
So please look forward to it! It will also be released on music distribution services, so please look forward to that too.
そしてですね、次が最後の曲になるんですけれども、ね、みんな楽しみに、きっと楽しみにしていたあの曲を歌います。
And now, this will be the last song, but... I will sing that song everyone has been looking forward to.
The next song is going to be the last song. Sad, but you guys will love this performance. I'll do my best.
Okay, onto the last song then. My new original song, Chronic.
yeah yeah yeah yeah
hey
walking round ' in reality i 'm so done , done
Walking round in reality, I'm so done, done
feel like i 'm losing my gravity
Feel like I'm losing my gravity
my vision of you that i see clearly in my mind
i 'm so you
I'm so you
my thoughts collide in my mind
i know i really should try to think , to think on my own , but oh -
I know I really should try to think, to think on my own, but oh
we 're tied together , it 's true
We're tied together, it's true
i think i 'm becoming you
I think I'm becoming you
don't blink , don't blink
Don't blink, don't blink
( i - i )
(I-I)
they 're asking who took me so far away , far away
They're asking who took me so far away, far away
digitally recreate everything
i wanna show you why i \uff5e [ parallel we rise ]
I wanna show you why I [Parallel we rise]
love it
chk - chk - boom
Chk-chk-boom
chronic , chronic , chronic collide till we go atomic
Chronic, chronic, chronic collide till we go atomic
turn it , turn it , turn it to a different space , different wave
Turn it, turn it, turn it to a different space, different wave
want it , want it , want it opposites go supersonic
Want it, want it, want it, opposites go supersonic
love it love it love it dive into the fate we made
sometimes i think you 're here , yeah you 're my only one
Sometimes I think you're here, yeah you're my only one
you make it feel so real , outside it 's so bizarre
You make it feel so real, outside it's so bizarre
devastation and creation ooh \uff5e i 'll be your shooting star
Devastation and creation ooh, I'll be your shooting star
a new perspective of life while i just try to survive
i know , i know we 're not going down
I know, I know we're not going down
i guess i can't compromise the in between of our lives
i know , i know ( i - i )
I know, I know (I-I)
you must be who took me so far away , far away
You must be who took me so far away, far away
digitally recreate everything
i \uff5e wanna show you why i \uff5e [ parallel we rise ]
I wanna show you why I [Parallel we rise]
love it
chk - chk - boom
Chk-chk-boom
chronic , chronic , chronic collide till we go atomic
Chronic, chronic, chronic collide till we go atomic
turn it , turn it , turn it to a different space , different wave
Turn it, turn it, turn it to a different space, different wave
want it , want it , want it opposites go supersonic
Want it, want it, want it, opposites go supersonic
love it love it love it dive into the fate we made
whisper come take me right away
Whisper
Merging right into you, oh my
Whisper, me and my only
Press and hold onto continue, it'll always be you
Tell me you won't go away
Imagining maybe one day
That we'll meet in between organic life and blue screens
I do need you
Mirror on the wall say, you'll take me so far
Chronic, collide 'til we go
Turn it, turn it, turn it to a different space, different wave
Want it, want it, want it, opposites go supersonic
Love it, love it, love it, dive into the fate we made
Whisper, come take me right away
Whisper, merging right into you, oh my
Whisper, me and my only
Press and hold onto continue, it'll always be you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah